premiertraderuniversity.com 2016-03-28

# Privacy Policy - Premier Trader University - Online Trading Courses

We respect each site visitor’s right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address.

The information we collect is:

used to improve the content of our Web page.  
used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site.  
used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes.  
used for 3rd party promotions and other complimentary offers.

Registration is not required to enter our site.

Premier Trader University occasionally uses the [AdRoll display advertising network](http://www.adroll.com/) to collect visitor data on our site and then serve targeted display ads to you on other sites. Our partners use technology such as cookies and web beacons to collect this data. For more information or to opt-out of this type of advertising, please visit [AdRoll’s privacy policy](http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy).

Premier Trader University uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using Google’s [Ad Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) page. Users can completely block Google Analytics tracking using [Google’s Opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Premier Trader University uses Facebook advertising and retargeting. Cookies and pixels are used to understand and deliver ads and make them more relevant to you. We may also use a cookie to learn whether someone who saw an ad on Facebook later visited our website.

We have an order form.

We require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and possibly financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). If we have trouble processing an order, we use the information to contact the user. This information is used:

for shipping and billing purposes.  
to fill customer´s orders.

We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site.

We publish a newsletter (ezine), and we never sell or share our subscribers’ email addresses.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to:

this privacy statement.  
other places we deem appropriate.

If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Email: info@premiertraderuniversity.com

Postal Address: 9400 MacArthur Blvd #124-417 Irving,TX 75063 USA

Website URL: http://www.premiertraderuniversity.com
